Finding Aid for the Carol Burnett Papers PASC.0066
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings, 1975-2003; Series 12.; 1 manuscript box; 1 flat box
  - Publishing proofs, What I Want to be When I Grow Up, 1975; 1 folder, 2 matted photos, 11"x16", color (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Matted publishing proofs for children's book of photographs featuring Carol Burnett called What I Want to be When I Grow Up; created by George Mendoza and Sheldon Secunda; New York: Simon and Schuster, 1975.
    (1 of 3)
  - Publishing proofs, What I Want to be When I Grow Up, 1975; 1 folder, 8 matted photos, 10'x15",color (Box 32, Folder 5)
    (2 of 3)
  - Publishing proofs, What I Want to be When I Grow Up, 1975; 1 folder, 12 matted photos, 10'x15",color (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Proofs in original order as found in portfolio; (3 of 3).
  - Publishing proofs, What I Want to be When I Grow Up, 1975; 1 folder; complete book, loose pages, 11"x16", b/w (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Publishing proofs for children's book of photographs featuring Carol Burnett called What I Want to be When I Grow Up; created by George Mendoza and Sheldon Secunda; New York: Simon and Schuster, 1975. Pages are numbered.
  - Publishing proofs, What I Want to be When I Grow Up, 1975; 1 folder, loose pages, color (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Publishing proofs for children's book of photographs featuring Carol Burnett called What I Want to be When I Grow Up; created by George Mendoza and Sheldon Secunda; New York: Simon and Schuster, 1975.
  - Publishing proofs, What I Want to be When I Grow Up, 1975; 1 folder, loose pages, color (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - What Becomes a Legend most? The Blackglama Story, 1979; Book (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Book of photographs of actress/entertainers wearing Blackglama fur coats; photos taken by Richard Avedon and Bill King; women featured include Carol Burnett, Lauren Bacall, Diana Ross; written by Peter Rogers, New York: Fireside, Simon and Schuster.
    Photographs of Carol Burnett taken for this book are located in s.s.6.4; box/folder 24/9.
  - Plaque of front and back book cover, One More Time, A Memoir, 1986; Wooden plaque, 25" x 12 1/2" (Box 61)
    Wooden plaque of the front and back book cover of Carol Burnett's, One More Time, A Memoir.
  - Writings of Robert W. Firestone, 1984; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 33)
    Four articles/academic papers written by Robert W. Firestone, The Glendon Association, Los Angeles, CA, on the topic of psychotherapy and family and parental bonds. Article titles include: "A Concept of the Primary Fantasy Bond: A Developmental Perspective," "The 'Voice': The Dual Nature of Guilt Reactions," "Destructive Bonds in Marital and Family Process," "Micro-Suicide and Suicidal Threats of Everyday Life."
  - One More Time: A Memoir, 2003; Proof of book cover, color (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Color proof of "One More Time: A Memoir" book cover.
- Music, 1958, 1965, undated; Series 13.
  This series contains music material not related to any of the other live performances, television programs or feature films listed as part of a series and/or sub-series (or clearly indicated as such).
  This series is arranged in chronological order.
  - "Destroy Me," by Carol Burnett, March 21, 1958; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Handwritten song lyrics, 4 loose pages; "for teleprompter" written on page, but no indication as to which show it was used for.
  - Arr. by Joe Hamilton, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    3 pages of blank sheet music marked: "arr. by joe hamilton [sic]."
  - He's Gone Away, January 29-30, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Conductor score (5 copies [1 Production].). Original folder marked: "7110 Show #19 Tape: 1/29/65 Air: 1/30/65 C. Burnett Silvio Franceso key: A [flat]." Orchestral parts in separate folder.
  - He's Gone Away (#12), January 29-30, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Entertainers Television. Orchestral parts: 1-5 Reed; 1-4 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Harp; A-C Violin; Viola; Cello; Piano.
  - Red Sails in the Sunset; Hi-Lili, Hi-Lo, undated; 2 published arrangements (Box 27, Folder 10)
    Contains published arrangements (music and lyrics) for Red Sails in the Sunset and Hi-Lili, Hi-Lo.
- Accession LSC-2006-005 backlog material, LSC-2006-005; 1.25 linear feet (1 flat box) (Box 1)